megalytic.com 2013-10-12

# Megalytic - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Last Updated April 18, 2012

Digital Brand Mine LLC (the “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) owns and operates MEGALYTIC.COM (the “Site”), along with web services related to the Site (collectively, the "Service"). This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes how the Company collects and uses information and data from users of the Service.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy or its enforcement, please contact the Company at [legal@megalytic.com](mailto:legal@megalytic.com).

As used herein, the terms “you” and “your” refer to you (together with the entity or other business for which you are registering at the Site or using the Service).

#### 1\. Personal Information

“Personal Information,” as used in this policy, is information that may be used to identify an individual, such as a person’s name, email address, or credit card number. 

##### A. How We Collect Personal Information

We collect Personal Information in the course of providing the Service to you, including through your voluntary, optional submissions, such as information that you provide to us at the time of registering for the Service, or through your use of the Service. When you register with us for an account, we may collect information such as your name and email address. When you pay for certain features of the Service, we may collect information such as your credit card number, expiration date, billing address, and CVV or security code number. You may also provide Personal Information to us in other ways, such as by requesting user support.

We may also receive Personal Information about you from third party data sources that you choose to connect to the Service (“Third Party Personal Information”), and may combine such information with other Personal Information we maintain about you. If we do so, this policy also applies to such Third Party Personal Information.

##### B. How We Use Personal Information

We use Personal Information that we collect to (a) provide, improve, and develop the Service, (b) tailor your user experience, (c) respond to your inquiries or requests, (d) prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of the Service, (f) conduct research and development, and (e) analyze trends, and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

In addition, we may use your email address to deliver product information and marketing messages. You may opt-out from receiving these marketing messages by following the instructions provided in such messages to unsubscribe or by emailing the address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

##### C. How We Share Personal Information

We may share Personal Information with our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of providing the Service and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We limit the Personal Information shared with these third parties to that which is reasonably necessary to carry out those functions.

We may also share Personal Information with third parties (including regulatory or law enforcement authorities) (a) in order to carry out a user’s request, or (b) if we believe that doing so is necessary (i) to conform or comply with any legal, regulatory, law enforcement or similar requirement or investigation, (ii) to protect or defend our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights or property of others or (iii) to enforce the Terms of Service.

If you post any of your information to a public area of the Service, please be aware that it is no longer “Personal Information” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, and we or anyone else may use such information without restriction. If you provide access to personal or other information, including your email address or name, to a limited set of other users through any of our privacy controls or other settings, please understand that the Company has no control over how others may collect, use, or disclose such information.

##### D. Non-Personal Information We Collect, and How We Use It

We may also collect information that is not personally identifiable, and may aggregate Personal Information or otherwise render it anonymous ( collectively, “Non-Personal Information). We may use Non-Personal Information that we collect to (a) provide, improve, and develop the Service and otherwise tailor your user experience, (b) prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Service, and (c) conduct research and development, and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also share Non-Personal Information with third parties. 

##### E. Usage Tracking and Passive Collection of Information

We may collect information from your use of the Service. For example, we may collect information about user traffic and usage patterns throughout our site, and similar information regarding the use of the Service. We may also track click-through information, such as IP addresses, from the messages we send to our users. We use the information we collect in these manners to, for example, improve our Service, to develop new products and services, to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, to discourage and address abusive and fraudulent use of our Service, and to help our users with troubleshooting issues.

We may also collect information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (“Web beacons”). When you visit the Site or use the Service, we may send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser or recognizes a cookie that is already on your machine. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, and to customize your experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, many aspects of the Service will not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Also, please be aware that third parties may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection.

If we directly combine any Non-personal Information gathered through passive means with Personal Information gathered through such means, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this policy. Otherwise, we use information collected by passive means in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable forms.

#### 2\. Children

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Any individual person who provides his or her Personal Information to us through the Service represents that he or she is older than 12 years of age. If we become aware that a person under 13 has provided Personal Information, the Company will take steps to remove such information and terminate the respective account. 

#### 3\. Our Commitment to Data Security

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect in association with the Service. Please be aware, however, that no data transmissions over the Internet or other networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us or that you authorize us to collect on your behalf. You transmit information to us, and authorize us to collect information on your behalf, at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

If the Company learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. The Company may post a notice through the Service if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to access the Service. The Company may also notify you via email in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

#### 4\. Third-Party Sites and Services

Our Service may contain links to or interoperate with third-party sites and services. Any links to or interoperability with third-party sites or services are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties. Any Personal Information that you provide to any other third party is subject to that third party’s privacy practices and policies, not this policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with Personal Information. 

#### 5\. Business Transfers

Information about our users, including Personal Information, may be disclosed to a successor to all or substantially all of the Company’s business or assets that concern the Service as part of a merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, or similar transaction or in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which Personal Information would be transferred as one of our business assets. In the event of such a transfer, such successor will have all of the rights and be subject to all of the obligations of this Privacy Policy. 

#### 6\. International Visitors

The Service is hosted in and provided from the United States of America (“USA”). If you use our Service from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from USA law, please note that by using the Service you are transferring your personal data to the USA. All matters relating to the Service are governed by the laws the State of New York, USA. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the USA and the storage, processing and use of your Personal Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### 7\. Information Retention and Disposal

We may retain Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for as long as we have a business need for it or applicable laws or regulations or government orders require us to retain it. For as long as all such information is retained, we will be subject to all of the obligations for the use and disclosure of such information set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

#### 8\. Changes and Updates

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to stay informed about our collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. 

#### 9\. How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us using the following contact information:

**Digital Brand Mine LLC**  
708 Third Avenue, 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10017
